but with this viewers let's move on and
it's time to highlight today's breakout
and breakdown counters firstly let's
focus on the breakdown stock and today
from the financial space we have seen a
weakness in a lot of counters but ICICI
Bank onto the charts because if you will
see the stock is seem to be making a
U-turn after forming a double top
pattern and not just that if you will
see the today's fall a major rejection
coming in from its 20-day moving average
and if you will see the stock also broke
its key support of 9 130 which was a
support for a past couple of weeks now
and today the stock was seen to be
trending lower 927 or Rupees is where
the stock ended and the move was also
supported by a short buildup on the
derivative side moving on the next
counter for today is on the breakout
side and farma stocks were showing
resilience the defensive pack coming in
once again to cheer up the market and
today D's lab onto the charts the stock
has been moving upwards has already
shown a good up move but for today a key
resistance was taken out
3550 rupees level of resistance for so
many times now was SE to be breaking out
and now the stock is SE to be trading
above all its key moving averages B 20
200 as well as 100 day moving average
and today's support was also supported
by long build up on the derivative side
so these are the two counters on the
breakout and break down side right and